// import React from "react";
// import Accordion from "./Accordion";

// function MyComponent() {
//   const data = [
//     {
//       id: 1,
//       Question: "Workstation Laptop Stand",
//       Answer:
//         "Adjustable stand to improve ergonomics while working on a laptop.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 2,
//       Question: "Smart LED Desk Lamp",
//       Answer: "Adjustable lamp with multiple brightness levels and colors.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 3,
//       Question: "Apple Cinnamon Granola",
//       Answer: "A wholesome granola with bits of apple and a touch of cinnamon.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 4,
//       Question: "Electric Heating Pad",
//       Answer:
//         "Microwaveable heating pad for muscle pain relief and relaxation.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 5,
//       Question: "DIY Candle Making Kit",
//       Answer: "Everything you need to make your own candles.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 6,
//       Question: "LED Desk Light",
//       Answer: "Adjustable LED desk light with brightness settings.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 7,
//       Question: "Caramelized Onion Dip Mix",
//       Answer: "A mix to create a delicious onion dip for parties or snacking.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 8,
//       Question: "Safety Pin Dispenser",
//       Answer: "Handy dispenser for quick access to safety pins.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 9,
//       Question: "Organic Baby Carrots",
//       Answer: "Fresh and crunchy baby carrots ready for snacking.",
//     },
//     {
//       id: 10,
//       Question: "Blueberry Oatmeal Cups",
//       Answer: "Instant oatmeal cups with blueberries for an easy breakfast.",
//     },
//   ];

//   return (
//     <div>
//       <Accordion data={data} defaultExpand={true}/>
//     </div>
//   );
// }

// export default MyComponent;
